Hot Springs Travel Association Insurange
Part 1
Yay!
What, 2 hours?
About 2 hours and a half.
It was a long trip!
Hey, I ran!
I'm so glad.
Hey, the weather is a little bit bad.
It's about to start raining.
But I'm looking forward to it.
We've been doing this for a long time.
We'll never make it here by ourselves.
It's a little difficult without a car.
It's a nice town, isn't it?
Yeah, it's really nice.
The air is so clean.
Let's go.
Oh, my God, the air is so clean.
Oh, I'm scared.
It's Tae-Yoo. Tae-Yoo.
What, Tayu?
Look, it's the mackerel.
It's good, right? It's okay.
Can I touch it?
Yes, you can.
Excuse me.
It's warm.
Oh, it's warm?
It's Taeyu.
It's so hot.
It's warm!
Did you touch it?
I want to touch it.
Oh, you're holding it right there.
Oh, my God.
But, but...
Can you do it?
Can I have a little bit of this?
Oh, it's warm.
It's warm.
Wow.
Oh, it's warm.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Can you see this, guys?
Over there.
Hot.
Saroo.
Saroo
Let's go.
Tofu?
Wow, what?
Gelato!
Gelato?
Not at all. Gelato.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's gelato!
This kind of place?
No, it's not.
Great. You want to try it?
Let's go.
It looks so good!
I want tofu!
Tofu.
Oh, man.
Looks delicious.
Tofu?
I want tofu.
Wasabi sounds good, too.
Tofu and vanilla can be mixed with fresh wasabi.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
What?
Gelato.
That's amazing.
I'm sorry, but...
What?
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Self-directed.
I'm self-directing.
Okay, then.
Vanilla.
One vanilla.
Yes, ma'am.
Tofu.
Three tofu.
Yes, sir.
All tofu and wasabi.
Yes.
All of it.
Tofu alone.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Give me a bite.
Later.
No, thank you.
It's good.
Delicious.
Yummy
Yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
Wasabi.
Wasabi is really new born now!
I've never heard of it being newborn.
Thank you very much.
This is absolutely delicious!
Eat up, Yuuchan.
Cheers!
First, let's keep the tofu the way it is.
Congratulations!
Wow, it's big!
Tofu!
Sorry, it's a little big!
I can feel it.
This is tofu, right?
Tofu, right?
It's tofu.
Delicious!
Wasabi.
Do you taste the wasabi?
Yes.
Tofu with wasabi.
The wasabi is not too spicy, so it's easy to eat.
Let's try some, Nen-chan.
Okay, I'll try it.
It's amazing!
It tastes like wasabi.
The wasabi is so refreshing.
It's like you're being wrapped in wasabi.
Tofu.
Yum!
Delicious?
Yes, it is.
It's sweet.
It's good, isn't it?
I thought maybe I could grab it.
I thought so, I thought so, I thought so.
Are you okay?
I thought you said it was all tofu.
It's delicious.
It's all curled up in a ball.
It's totally fine.
Maybe not too spicy?
It's not spicy at all.
It's okay, it's a little spicy at first.
Wait, it's tofu.
Tofu?
Tofu? Is it really tofu?
Yes, it is.
Ajax.
It's the aroma, isn't it?
It's delicious.
But it's kind of sweet.
Just sweet.
Tofu.
Vanilla or tofu? Which one?
Huh? Vanilla.
I'm still a little late.
You're a bit...
My mouth.
Let's go next time.
Did you eat?
Thank you very much.
I hope you're feeling better today.
It's always easy to smile
Wait, guys.
Oh, no, this is bad.
Oh, no, this is bad!
But wait.
Isn't this better?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
It's a hot spring!
Then I want to jump in.
I know, I know!
I want to jump in!
Why?
What? A picture of Honochan?
I want to jump in!
Here we go!
Yes, she's cute!
Very nice!
That's great.
It's so cute.
Thank you so much for the ride.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, my God.
What do you know about this?
I should've made a wish while I was crossing.
I guess.
That wish came true.
If you make a wish while crossing
Your wish will be fulfilled
We've already crossed once.
I want to jump in so bad!
Cancel
Undo it.
Come here and undo it!
Undo.
Cancel once.
Once.
Once zero.
Cancel.
One more time, because I fly a lot when I come back like this.
Wow.
Coaching here!
What?
I don't know, I think it's over there.
Right there.
You can't read!
Something over there.
There.
You can read that distance?
Okay, then.
Here you go.
All right.
All right. - All right.
You're supposed to read it.
Sorry about the cloaking.
Let's do it right.
Croaching.
Cloze it up.
All right, all right.
Let's do it right!
Let's do it right. Let's do it right.
I've got it
That's it.
Here you go.
Yes, sir.
Is this the kind of thing you can say out loud?
Not in your mind? I see what you mean.
Thank you very much.
And by the way, what did you say?
What?
May you become millionaires.
And the pine tree?
May you be popular.
And me, too, may I be the one behind the scenes.
I wish you all the best.
This is the place where humanity's
The economy.
It's where my sense of humanity comes out.
We played rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
It's not an afterthought.
That's not true.
You know, I'm sure you all saw that I was playing goo, so you played par.
It's so delicious.
Ayu!
Wait, grilled ayu.
Wait!
One more time.
One more time later.
Wait a minute.
Wait!
I'll eat.
I'll have one of these.
One?
Excuse me.
Is it okay if I film this?
It's the Wachter recipe room next door.
Yes, sir.
Something on YouTube?
Here you go, YouTube.
Ayu?
Thank you very much.
Please give me an ayu.
You film it yourself?
Ayu.
If you like something...
I like it.
Make two and share them with everyone.
Sure.
Ayu.
Looks so delicious!
Sorry for the short notice.
Thank you very much.
It's flame ayu.
Is this the first time I've grilled ayu with salt?
What?
One more?
Yes.
This is how you eat it.
You ate it at the chef's, Ayu.
Yes.
That's not Ayu.
It's ayu.
It's all we have.
Bon appétit!
How do you eat it?
Like this.
Can we eat it like this?
I don't know.
Like a betoro.
Yeah, I thought so.
Come on, Homé, go ahead.
Go ahead, please.
Is it good?
It's not good, is it?
I know it's bad.
Take another bite.
It's too salty.
You said it was salty.
Salty.
It's salty.
Oh, man, that's bad.
I guess that's just one more.
Oh, there he goes.
I think I'm going to get a filet.
Hire.
I'm not sure I knew it, but he says he's listening to West.
How's that? That's a lot!
I'll eat it here.
You can do it, right?
Can you fly?
Let's split it in half.
Thank you very much.
Target practice.
I love target practice.
So retro!
What's this place?
Retro!
Retro
Good morning.
Oh, my God.
It's not target practice.
We'll do it two at a time.
Let's do it.
Team game.
That's good.
Good-percenters.
Good par.
All right, I'll take it.
All right.
Good par.
I'll do it later.
I'm gonna do it.
Let's say goodbye at 10:00 a.m.
Let's split up.
After all...
We're in this together.
We're going to win.
I'll do it.
I'll take care of it.
Yoo-chan, please.
Okay, then.
Hit with this thin ball.
Just a little.
Push it with your 10-year-old thumb.
This is it. Keep it in like this.
Pew.
Ooh.
That was really close.
Now don't move it.
I'm going to pull it with a cleaning brush.
Yes, sir.
Wow.
Oh, is this okay?
I want to pull one of these.
Thank you very much
20 points for anyone who can add all of these.
Good luck, and don't miss.
Yes, sir.
Good luck.
If Yoo-chan misses once, it's true...
If you miss once, you're almost guaranteed to win.
There's a chance you'll miss.
Ikeden-chan.
You're in a good position, Seki-chan.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Turducken.
Stop it!
That's the worst way to cheer
Ooh!
Ew!
If it's a double here, it's a double first.
Yes, sir.
Yay!
Oh, shit.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
First one down, two to go.
I'm sure of it. I'm sure of it.
Why? Why?
How do you do that?
It's like knocking over dominos.
No, but wait.
The angle is so hard.
It's just about right.
You did it! You did it!
That's how it's done.
That's what I mean.
Double.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's go for a double or a triple.
Heh heh heh heh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'll take my chances and pull it off, I'm sure we're all feeling the same way...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
wait, wait, wait, frustrating, frustrating, wait a minute, wait a minute, dad, dad, give me a ride, give me a ride, give me a ride, give me a ride, give me a ride, give me a ride
Daddy, please give me a ride!
I'm going to triple for sure!
What do you say, "like this"?
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. One, clean one, clean one, clean one.
Nice, nice, nice.
Oh, my God, that's great.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Number three, number four
Tencho, you're number 4? Oh, my God!
Lapland Rivendell, you're going to be a princess.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
We're princesses. We're princesses. We're princesses.
We're Princesses!
We're princesses, we're princesses!
Almost super cute.
Look, look, look.
What's going on?
This one won't open.
It won't open.
What do you mean, one at a time? I don't know how to do it.
Oh, no, it's like this. It's like this. It's like this.
This way?
Oh, my God, look at this.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow!
Oh, no! What should I do?
What? Make it?
Yay!
What's wrong with you?
Yay.
Making?
Let's hear the next sound. Wait, why don't you just stay over there?
Shut up! I was just listening.
I was just listening. - Let's go over there and listen closer.
I'm listening.
What?
You know, the first person who wasn't interested was on a bike.
Kara, kara, kara, kara.
I was unfocused.
I'm not focused.
They're all gone.
Oh, I'm so excited.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm waiting.
Ta-da!
There you go.
This is where we're going today.
Wait a minute.
Where Yui didn't come in.
Alone.
Anywhere's fine
Thanks for the roof.
Wait, the smell is so bad.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
The smell is really bad
Hello, there.
Stop it!
Give me your hand, Yuichan.
Yui, give me your hand.
Come home.
Please
It's called "onsen no okoke
Yui, please
Yui, please!
I came here for the first time today.
Yuiichan
It's so good!
Can you offer me something good?
I think it's good
I will be invited to the party
That's great
We're going out.
It looks like we're going outside.
But... but...
Wait, wait, wait.
I have chopsticks.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Oh, no.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
This is good.
Hey, yukomo-yukomo-yukomo-yukomo-yukomo-yukomoto.
Stop it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Cette.
What's this?
What do you mean?
what kind of thing is this?
other words
Quickly
Kh Nabai
Cues
Neutral
N
U
Really
yeah
Mm
Image.
Very much.
No.
Not as much as I thought.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Please turn around
Seino
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no!
What? It's really an open-air bath!
Gachimon!
It's my first time here.
This is bad
Six times, six times, six times
All right, let's go in, let's go in, let's go in.
Ready, go!
Oh, wait, that's great, that's great, that's bad.
Oh, my God.
But isn't it raining a little less than before? Rain.
Hey, I thought...
I'm gonna have to shut up.
You're right.
We don't have to wait.
I'm glad we did the lead change.
I'm so glad we did it.
How long have you been together?
Almost one year.
That was a fun day.
That was fun.
That last scene at the ocean.
We've been having so much fun.
It was a lot of work.
Even the paint thing was fun.
It was like we were really young.
I wish we had done it after that.
I'm glad we did it after that.
You know...
Cloudy skies are great, but...
If it was a sunset...
She's crying.
Thank God it's cloudy, really.
So, this is...
This is the main one, in case you were wondering.
I don't know. It's okay.
It was fun before that.
Looks good.
Oh, this?
Of course.
Can I leave these on?
Sure.
You can leave your shoes on.
It looks really good.
I'm in a hurry, in a hurry, in a hurry.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I feel like crying.
Thank you very much for the water.
I'm so happy about the water.
The sashimi is absolutely delicious.
Sashimi like marbled meat!
Thank you so much!
It's too delicious!
The fat melts in your mouth!
I've never had sashimi like this!
Busy, busy, busy.
Busy, busy. So delicious, so busy.
No, it's not.
Sashimi with salt.
Is it good? Delicious.
You're already desperate to eat.
That's all right.
I'm happy.
It's delicious.
I'm a boring person when I have a really good meal in front of me.
But you know, when we go out to eat together...
And when we're eating, we're usually quiet.
The tension in the video I took in my head and the tension now...
It's too different.
It's dyed-in-the-wool.
What?
I got water poisoning.
Well, I guess that's that.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, it's dyed.
It means we can be both sides of the same coin.
Yeah, there's a lot of sides to you.
Mm-hmm. Many sides.
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Mm.
Mmm.
Let's ding the garlic, put some salt on it, and eat it with the garlic.
That's good.
What was that?
Can you just listen to me one more time? All of you.
Let's eat the garlic with the salt.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, okay.
It's good.
Let's hear you say it.
Let's eat garlic with salt on it.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
The comment section is full of "yes.
It's going to be full of "yeses.
Let's all eat hand in hand.
Thank you very much for the food.
Thank you for the food.
It was very delicious.
Clap your hands.
Applause
How was everyone's lunch time today?
Great!
Let's do it!
If you want to go to the hot springs, please click the "Good" button, give us a high rating, and join us! Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you very much!
That's all for now, this is the Onsen Submission Party!
Bye bye!